mariogames1.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of **mariogames1.com**.  
**  
** We can be reached via e-mail at [mariogames1@gmail.com](mailto:)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
* Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here up-to-date at March 13, 2009](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557)

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here third-party vendors](https://www.google.com/support/adsense/bin/answer.py?answer=94149)

\-- 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://networkadvertising.org.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.

we uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://valueclickmedia.com/webuser_privacy.shtml.

\-- 

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by Email us at the address provided above.

From time to time, we make our _customer_ e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by E-mail us at the address provided above.ok-2010
